<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fiction on Finding The Way Home</title>
    <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/tags/fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fiction on Finding The Way Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 10:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/tags/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Businessman &amp; the fisherman</title>
      <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/the-businessman-and-fisherman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/the-businessman-and-fisherman/</guid>
      <description>An American businessman took a vacation to a small coastal Mexican village on doctor’s orders. Unable to sleep after an urgent phone call from the office the first morning, he walked out to the pier to clear his head. A small boat with just one fisherman had docked, and inside the boat were several large yellowfin tuna. The American complimented the Mexican on the quality of his fish.
“How long did it take you to catch them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purpose of Education</title>
      <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/the-purpose-of-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 1948 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/the-purpose-of-education/</guid>
      <description>As I engage in the so-called &amp;ldquo;bull sessions&amp;rdquo; around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the &amp;ldquo;brethren&amp;rdquo; think that education should equip them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out to Sea</title>
      <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/out-to-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 1912 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/out-to-sea/</guid>
      <description>I had this story from one who had no business to tell it to me, or to any other. I may credit the seductive influence of an old vintage upon the narrator for the beginning of it, and my own skeptical incredulity during the days that followed for the balance of the strange tale.
When my convivial host discovered that he had told me so much, and that I was prone to doubtfulness, his foolish pride assumed the task the old vintage had commenced, and so he unearthed written evidence in the form of musty manuscript, and dry official records of the British Colonial Office to support many of the salient features of his remarkable narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking-Glass house</title>
      <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/looking-glass-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 1871 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/looking-glass-house/</guid>
      <description>One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it:— it was the black kitten’s fault entirely. For the white kitten had been having its face washed by the old cat for the last quarter of an hour (and bearing it pretty well, considering); so you see that it couldn’t have had any hand in the mischief. The way Dinah washed her children’s faces was this: first she held the poor thing down by its ear with one paw, and then with the other paw she rubbed its face all over, the wrong way, beginning at the nose: and just now, as I said, she was hard at work on the white kitten, which was lying quite still and trying to purr — no doubt feeling that it was all meant for its good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down The Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/down-the-rabbit-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 1865 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/down-the-rabbit-hole/</guid>
      <description>Alice was beginning to get very tired of sitting by her sister on the bank, and of having nothing to do: once or twice she had peeped into the book her sister was reading, but it had no pictures or conversations in it, &amp;lsquo;and what is the use of a book,&amp;rsquo; thought Alice &amp;lsquo;without pictures or conversation?&amp;rsquo;
So she was considering in her own mind (as well as she could, for the hot day made her feel very sleepy and stupid), whether the pleasure of making a daisy-chain would be worth the trouble of getting up and picking the daisies, when suddenly a White Rabbit with pink eyes ran close by her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gettysburg Address</title>
      <link>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/gettysburg-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 1863 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljhrot.github.io/hasper/gettysburg-address/</guid>
      <description>Fourscore and seven years ago our fathers brought forth on this continent, a new nation, conceived in Liberty, and dedicated to the proposition that all men are created equal.
Now we are engaged in a great civil war, testing whether that nation, or any nation so conceived and so dedicated, can long endure. We are met on a great battle-field of that war. We have come to dedicate a portion of that field, as a final resting place for those who here gave their lives that that nation might live.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>